inspiringquotes.in 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Inspiring Quotes for Spiritual and Personal Growth

At [www.inspiringquotes.in](http://inspiringquotes.in/), we care for the privacy of our visitors.

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used. This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. We request you should visit it regularly.  Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

**Personal Information**  
If you subscribe with us or send us an email, we will never share your email address with any third parties.  
We do not requests user to share your personal information or any other information.

**Information Logs**

We make use of some code to keep a track of  the user’s ip address, browser, operating system and device When a user views a page, image or other item on this site.

The sole purpose of this information is to improve the experience of the website. None of the information is publicly available nor it is shared with anyone.

**Cookies and Advertising**  
A cookie is a piece of information stored on the user’s browser by a website, which can be read later. A cookie may be used to remember something about a user. Users may choose not to accept cookies through privacy settings in most web browsers. The relevant setting can usually be found in a ‘Privacy’ section under the browser’s options dialog. Refer to your web  browser’s documentation for more information.

It is possible to use this site even if your browser is configured to reject cookies.

We do not store or retrieve any personally identifiable information about users through our use of cookies.

Advertisers on this site store and read cookies on the user’s browser, and collect other statistical information which they use to display relevant advertisements on the site based on the content.

We do not have any access to the information from these cookies and they are not used to store or retrieve any personally identifiable information about users.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f794989983969483b79e9984879e859e9990868298839284d99e99 "contact@inspiringquotes.in")
